life system
------------
healing
each player starts with a +25h kit
a group upgrade can be made to upgrade these kit to +50h
+25h kit takes 3s to be used, 7s if moving
+50h kit takes 5s to be used, 15 if moving
if moving, healing speed switch to moving speed, taking 1s after stopping.

the team can buy only one medic's training book each 5 rounds, allowing only one player at a time ro heal with +25h kit in 2s (has max 5 kits), +50h kit in 5s (has  max 2kits) (kits start at their max, 1 kit is added each round, can be bought)

a player can use his own kit on another player
a kit cannot be applied before 90sec after the kit ended to be applied


each players life is doubled at a new round
can upgrade to triple
---------
life status
after the resistance bar hits 0, the player cannot move, his vision and hearing are limited (vision blurred and limited to a 15 m radius, perfect at 1 m, asymptotically seeable at 15 m.) (same for hearing, but at a 25 m radius)
depending on the weapon the player was hurt the most (only the two first are taken into consideration), the player will either start a die timer, or a waking up timer.

DEATH
A die timer mean that if the player is not rescued within 90s, he dies : he is basically considerated as a casualty taken to an hospital, and will be alive the round next to the round after.
if the round is won, the player is considered rescued and will be able to play at the next round.
after going out of an hospital, player has 90% running speed (but 100% running speed), and 75% wound resistance. these effects fade after 1min45s

STUN
each player has a conscience bar. when it is 25%, the player has 50% running speed for 3s and 75% until it rises to a normal maximum regenerated 50%, the bar regenerating 2 times faster if stopped and downed.

A restart kit comes with a electrocardio stuff, and some shit (really). it is not easy to know if a player is dying or just stunned, but can learn to know depending of the weapon used on the player, the blood around, or if rag doll indicates something, like still living muscles.
If electrocardio stuff is used, the player will randownly wake up or die of a heart attack if eletrized 3 times, with a 1/2 chance to be waken up. if electrostuffed 2 times, a 90% running speed is applied, and stun bar lose 50% regenerating rate for 15s.
If shit is used, the player will randomly do nothing if dying or the played will tell you "No. I prefer cookies. Gimme cookies" with 2% chance. If stunned, he will wake up.

If revived with electruff after a dying timer, the player fade away, taken to the hostpital.

It's not eletruff or else, just some kit to quickly revive a player. Ask a med.

------
stun weapons :
gum/soft balls
elesctrun lsrun
neck/head hit
tranquilizer : hitting place takes effect, depending on how high the syringe planted. the played cannot be waken up for the 25 or 50 s after being hit (depending on the tranquilizer fluid). all trqlz take the same time to take effect, from 1 to 45 s a timer starts when a player apply a syringe

standard syringe falls after 25 s, better ones after 10 s

death weapon :
shrapnel bullet
piercing bullet
poison
instant death : cyanure, too close nade
all players always equiped with a standard thin helmet that prevents instant headshot deaths : absorbing energy
-----
hearing system
noise hearing through depends on : 
- wall's materials (is there a closed door, is this a bunker, is it just a thin metal or plastic-like wall, or is it a noise-proof room ?).
- walking distance the sound needs to travel
- echoes
When a noise distance-gain is calculated, there are the wall factor (type of wall), and the room factor. If the room has a structure where eacho can happen, sounds will be better heard. example of structure : 2 heavy and large concrete parallel walls will echo more than 2 normal wood non-parallel walls. echo factor is ignored in non-large rooms, and are static, dictated by the map compiler (can be modified)
